Guide to the TEX Publications Collection SC1197
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
TEX publications collection
1979-2010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Ryus, Phyllis
SC1197
1.75 Linear Feet
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical / Historical
TeX Live is a free software distribution for the TeX typesetting system that includes major TeX-related programs, macro packages, and fonts. The project was originally started by Sebastian Rahtz in 1996 in collaboration with the TeX users groups worldwide, including the TeX Users Group. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/TeX_Live
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of TeX discs and publications manuals.
TeX (Computer system).; Computer programs.; Computer programming.; Ryus, Phyllis
- Publications
  - PC Tex Manual 2nd Edition, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - PC TEX Manual 3rd edition, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Latex User's Guide and Reference Manual, 1986 Sep (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lams-tex Version 2.0 Supplement, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lams-tex The Synthesis, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Texbook, 17th printing, 1990 Jan (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Textbook, 8th printing, 1986 Aug (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - PC Tex for Windows, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Joy of Tex, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Tex and Metafont, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Tex for the Beginner, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Personal Tex Inc. 1990 Catalog (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - MAXview: screen drivers for Tex, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - PC Tex 4th Edition, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Tex by Topic: A Texnician's Reference, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Latex for Everyone, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - User Manual MathType 4, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The New Standard Latex, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - MathTime: Postscript fonts for typesetting mathematics, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Texniques: Publications for the Tex Community Number 6 The PicTex Manual, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - PC Tex for Windows, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Tex Collection DVD, 2009 Oct (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tex/Latex CD 1 of 3, 1999 Jun (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Tex/Latex CD 2 of 3, 1999 Jun (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Tex Collection DVD, 2007 Feb (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Tex Collection DVD, 2008 Sep (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Protext, 2007 Feb (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Tex Live, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Tex Users Group, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Texniques: Publications for the Tex Community Number 8 A Users' Guide for Tex, 1987 Sep (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Texniques: Publications for the Tex Community Number 9 An Introduction to Latex, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Texniques: Publications for the Tex Community Number 11 First Grade Tex, 1983 Nov (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Texniques: Publications for the Tex Community Number 12 A Gentle Introduction to Tex, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - First Grade Tex A Beginner's Manual, 1983 Nov (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Proceedings EuroTex Conference 2009 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Tex Users Group Membership List, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Mathematical Typography, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Tex Users Group 10th Anniversary, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Tugboat TUG-NET (Technical and User Groups Network), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - EuroBachoTex Paths to the Future, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - EuroTex, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Tex Made Easy, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Software, Accession ARCH-2015-111
  - TEX Live 4, 1999-3; 1.1; 1 optical disc(s) (Box 1)
  - TEX Live 6, 2001-8; 1.2; 1 optical disc(s) (Box 1)
  - TEX Live 7 (Disk 1 of 2), 2002-6; 1.3; 1 optical disc(s) (Box 1)
  - TEX Live 7 (Disk 2 of 2), 2002-6; 1.4; 1 optical disc(s) (Box 1)
  - TEX Live, 2005; 1.5; 1 optical disc(s) (Box 1)
  - TEX Live ProText, 2005; 1.6; 1 optical disc(s) (Box 1)
  - TEX Collection, 2005; 1.7; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 1)
  - TEX Collection, 2008-9; 1.8; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 1)
  - TEX Collection, 2010-8; 1.9; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 1)